{
    "totalGameQue":10,
    "perQuestionTime":30,
    "questionArray":[
        {
            "question":"Which is the largest country in the world?",
            "answer":"Russia"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country has the largest population in the world?",
            "answer":"China"
        },
        {
            "question":"In which country would you find the Leaning Tower of Pisa?",
            "answer":"Italy"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the hottest continent on Earth?",
            "answer":"Africa"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the coldest place on Earth?",
            "answer":"Antarctica"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which continent is Britain part of?",
            "answer":"Europe"
        },
        {
            "question":"Where are the Andes mountains located?",
            "answer":"South America"
        },
        {
            "question":"From whom did the USA purchase Alaska from?",
            "answer":"Russia"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which countries have pyramids older than egypt?",
            "answer":"Sudan"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country is also known as the Netherlands?",
            "answer":"Holland"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the country with the most number of capital cities?",
            "answer":"South Africa"
        },
        {
            "question":"Ceylon is the former name of which country?",
            "answer":"Sri Lanka"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the smallest country in Asia by population?",
            "answer":"The Maldives"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which is the smallest country in the world?",
            "answer":"Vatican City"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country is called the Land of Rising Sun?",
            "answer":"Japan"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which European country shares its border with the most neighbors?",
            "answer":"Germany"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country shares the same peninsula as Portugal?",
            "answer":"Spain"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which country is Taj Mahal in?",
            "answer":"India"
        }
        ,
        {
            "question":"Which country was once known as Rhodesia?",
            "answer":"Zimbabwe"
        }
        ,
        {
            "question":"Which is the country with the least population?",
            "answer":"Vatican City"
        }
        ,
        {
            "question":"Which South American country has land borders with ten other countries?",
            "answer":"Brazil"
        }
        ,
        {
            "question":"Which country is the second biggest in the world?",
            "answer":"Canada"
        }
        ,
        {
            "question":"Which European country has a capital city called Bucharest?",
            "answer":"Romania"
        },
        {
            "question":"Which European country is closest to the continent of Africa?",
            "answer":"Spain"
        }
    ]
}